http://www.hollandforyou.com/hollandforyou-dutch-products/hollandforyou-dutch-groceries/welkom-hollandforyou-dutch-groceries/dutch-groceries-pterms-of-service

HomeLanguages
DutchEnglishNorwegianChineseGermanyFranceDutch ArtI AMSTERDAMView ProductsSALE SALEDUTCH FOODBABY & CHILDDUTCH DRINKSNON FOODDUTCH CANDYHEALTH & CAREDUTCH RECIPESDENTAL CAREBEAUTY CAREDUTCH HOUSEHOLD KITCHEN STUFF DUTCH BOOKSGIFTS TO GIVELogin/-outDutch RecipesCheckout/CartContactAbout UsRead ReviewTerms of servicePrivacy statementYour product requestCustomer Service(T&T) Track OrderDelivery RatesGet DiscountFree Shipping NL/EUR*Help Creditcard payment
Cart empty
NEW: Fast shipping via   (worldwide delivery within 1-8 days)
Hollandforyou.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information provided by visitors to our web sites. We have created the following guidelines to demonstrate our commitment to the issue of privacy. All information collected is for internal use by Hollandforyou.com only and will not be given, loaned, rented, traded or sold to any other party except in the following circumstances: Public surveys users agree to participate in. Billing and/or transaction agency used to perform customer transaction, in this case the billing agency will have it's own privacy policy. Under conditions of claims dispute, fraud or illegal activity a customers information maybe given to a collection agency or legal authorities. Our affiliate program will indicate when a customer has purchased a product as result of a referral but never a name, address, email or any private information, only that SOMEONE has made purchase for X amount of dollars on date and time.
Our web server automatically recognizes and collects the domain name and IP address of visitors to our web sites. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web pages, products and services.
Parts of this site may use cookies, which are stored on the users system, to keep track of customers purchases in order to properly credit our affiliates. The only information that outside affiliates will receive about customers activities will be limited to purchase amounts, dates and times. Never will an affiliate be given any name, email, IP number or personal information.
Terms of Service
The following information describes our policy as applied to sales, all potential customers should read these this before making a purchase. When a customer purchases a product from Hollandforyou.com they automatically agree and become bound to the terms even if they have not read them. Payment MethodsWe offer online purchasing via Paypal including creditcards Visa®, MasterCard®, American Express®. We also except Money Orders. Orders placed on-line using PayPal as a method for transaction will generate an e-mail to the customer confirming the order. We will then also confirm the order via e-mail or phone within 48 hours. email with subject: payment accepted.Order confirmation & Shipment Your order will be checked and manually accepted by us, normally withing 48 hours. We will send you an email once your order is shipped containing your tracking number. The normall shipment time ( see delivery rates) is an indication, no guarantee. Parcels may be subject to unforeseen delays at the Post or Customs. Hollandforyou.com has no control over this and cannot be held liable for that.Tracking Shipment is responsibility of customer.When the parcel is sent to the customer, it is the responsibility of the customer to check on a regular base the status of the shipment. If the customer does not have the tracking information, please contact hollandforyou to get a tracking link.  When there is no updated information about the the parcel the customer must contact local Customes, local Post office or contact hollandforyou within 7 days of last  tracking scan.Pricing and AvailabilityPrices, services, weight and availability of products are subject to change at any time and without notice. We also try offer products and services at a reasonable market price.Return PolicyIn general, all items are non-returnable. However, if an item needs to be returned ( baby products of formula excluded), which will be at the customer's expense, it has to be done within 7 days. A full credit will be applied, minus shipping costs, to your credit card. The goods must be unopened and in perfect condition in order for you to receive a refund.
Privacy Policy
Hollandforyou.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information provided by visitors to our web sites. We have created the following guidelines to demonstrate our commitment to the issue of privacy. All information collected is for internal use by Hollandforyou.com only and will not be given, loaned, rented, traded or sold to any other party except in the following circumstances: Public surveys users agree to participate in. Billing and/or transaction agency used to perform customer transaction, in this case the billing agency will have it's own privacy policy. Under conditions of claims dispute, fraud or illegal activity a customers information maybe given to a collection agency or legal authorities. Our affiliate program will indicate when a customer has purchased a product as result of a referral but never a name, address, email or any private information, only that SOMEONE has made purchase for X amount of dollars on date and time.
Our web server automatically recognizes and collects the domain name and IP address of visitors to our web sites. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web pages, products and services.
Parts of this site may use cookies, which are stored on the users system, to keep track of customers purchases in order to properly credit our affiliates. The only information that outside affiliates will receive about customers activities will be limited to purchase amounts, dates and times. Never will an affiliate be given any name, email, IP number or personal information.Shipping method
All shipping parcels are photographed. Shipping parcels through Europe and World wide and above  2 kg are insured. The parcels under 2 kg can be send with Track and trace and insurance or without track and trace number, the customer can select wether to send with insurance or without it track and trace. Sending parcels uninsured and without track and trace are the responsibility of the customer.
Joomla SEF URLs by Artio
LOGIN / LOGOUT
LOGIN       REGISTRATION       (Please login first when ordering)
SHOPPING CART
x
Cart empty
SHOPPINGSALE SALE
Dutch Products on SaleDUTCH FOOD
BakingBreakfast & LunchDutch CookingAsian CookingInproba OrientalDutch SoupDutch Meals MixDutch Meat / SausageCanned VegetablesCanned SaucesCookies / BiscuitsDutch CheeseSnacks & ChipsSyrup WafflesSuperFoodsDUTCH DRINKS
Cold DrinksHot DrinksBABY & CHILD
Aptamilk (milk powder)Hero (Milk powder)HippKruitvat (Milk powder)Nutrilon (Milk powder)Zwitsal Baby CareOlvarit (Baby Food)Baby CareBaby CookiesBebivita (Milk powder)BambixDUTCH CANDY
Venco LicoriceAH CandyAuto dropCote d'or chocFruit tella candyHaribo CandyIce lolliesJumbo DropKatja candyKlene DropKlene Drop 1kgLook o Look candyMilka ChocolateOther CandyNapoleon CandyRedband CandyTony's ChocolonelyVenco Bag 1kgGood StuffHalal CandyKinder EggsMentosNON FOOD
DetergentHemaBaby & Child BooksKitchen productsNovels BooksHEALTH & CARE
Dutch Diet FoodGluten-freeLactose FreeSugar FreeVegetarian FoodMedicineSkin CareBaby & Child CareFor WomenDental CareVitemins & MinaralsSuperFoods
KEEP CALM
PAYMENT INFO
LOGINSHOPPING CARTFOODDRINKBABY / CHILDDUTCH RECIPESDENTAL CAREBEAUTY CAREHEALTHHOUSEHOLDKITCHEN STUFFBOOKSBEST BRANDS
